I have one thousand two hundred seventy eight reais in the account
and twenty-one days to set up a business.
and today is the first day that I will invest
in my idea.
Get up,
get up,
Stay on the
it's still the same uncle.
the things i need to find in stores
for a change it doesn't.
come on, let's go.
And use your palm,
Stay on the scene
Like a sex machine,
You got to have the feeling,
Shoot your bones,
Get it together
Right on,
Right on.
the guys face seeing me with a selfie stick,
O valeu,
valeu,
it's trickery.
fisherman who catches big fish
invest in bait
be able to buy all things.
today there was no sale,
but had investment
let's get those ideas going there.
that was the nineth,
twenty-one days left for me to create my business.
if you want to know
really what I'm up to,
You're going to have to find that out tomorrow.
tamo together.